JORDAN DIABY

Mobile: +44 (0) 758 526 1763 | Email: Jordandiaby@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a confident communicator with excellent presentation skills, who is able to engage successfully at all levels and build effective working relationships. My previous academic and work experiences prepared to work within a number of varied environments and the ability to work well within a team. I have professional fluency in Italian, English.

EDUCATION

School of Oriental and African Studies, London

10/2017 - 01/2019

M.A. in Pacific Asian Studies

Exchange: National University of Singapore, Asia Research Institute

King's College London, London

09/2014 - 07/2017

B.A. in European Politics

Exchange: Tsinghua University in Beijing and The Chinese University of Hong Kong

EXPERIENCE

The Conduit, London

06/2018 - 12/2018

Intern, Client Relations (Membership)

- Maintained membership records up-to-date using CRM for all existing and potential members
- Managed the Membership and Nomination Inboxes, responding to all member queries
- Coordinated the onboarding process of newly signed up members in the opening period

Globe Locums, London 10/2017 – 12/2017

Intern, Compliance

- Monitored between 50-100 daily reports to track any compliance documentation due to expire and ensured timely renewal of candidates on the database
- Accountable for managing the pre-employment checking process, which includes performing all relevant checks in a timely manner before the candidate's expected start date
- Contacted candidates on a daily basis to request outstanding documentation needed for company's records

PAM (Private Asset Managers) Insight, London

10/2016 - 08/2017

Intern, Client Relations

- First point of contact for gathering financial data from over 100 London based wealth management firms including family offices for the PAM Directory
- Updated over 800 client's records on the firm's database
- Provided logistical support for the PAM Awards (regarded as the highest UK wealth management awards) by monitoring the events inbox during the period, adding guests to the list, and manage the firm's courier services

OTHER SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

Languages:

Italian (Native), English (Fluent), French (Fluent), Spanish (Conversational)

Database:

Salesforce (Intermediate), NorthStar (Intermediate)

Volunteering:

King's College London, Student-Staff Liaison Representative

05/2015 - 06/2017 01/2018 - 02/2018

Asia-European Foundation, Australia and New Zeeland

05/2013 - 10/2013

Raleigh International, Nicaragua

Certificates:

International Citizen Service Certificate

ASDAN Award Certificate: Level 3 Award in Community Volunteering

King's Experience Global Award

References available upon request